[Music] there's
[Música]
been a lot of gossip, really, really,
ha habido un salseo fuerte fuerte fuerte
eh December starts off badly, eh
eh empieza mal diciembre totalmente eh
December starts off badly,
empieza mal diciembre totalmente
guys, it starts off badly, eh Also, I think
chavales empieza mal eh Además yo creo
the next live show will already drop below
que el próximo directo Ya bajamos de los
2000, eh Javi Remember that gossip is
2000 eh Javi Recuerda que el chisme es
like bad grass that never dies. Ugh, I
como la mala Hierba nunca muere Uf yo
think you remember in 2019 when
creo que la os acordáis en 2019 cuando
the cotilleando forum members had a
las foreras de cotilleando Tenían un
thread exclusively to publish
hilo exclusivamente para ir publicando
the member counter, that is, because
el contador de miembros o sea porque que
I went from Yunou to YouTube and then of
yo me fui de yunou a YouTube y entonces
course as
claro conforme iban pasando la semana
the week went by, the members of Yunou were going down, do you remember, and they made drawings of a slide going down and things like that, brutal, that, eh, brutal. Let's see, today I published a pretty powerful clip on Twitter, I think it also appeared in the news, okay,
que también ha salido en el noti vale
but let's take a look at everything that's
pero vamos a ver un poco todo lo que
going on between Aida and Wescol because
está pasando entre Aida y wescol porque
Aida accuses Wescol of doing
Aida acusa a wescol de estar haciendo
things behind the scenes that have ended up
cosas por detrás que han terminado
exhausting themselves
agotándose
that could ruin him, well, not that they could ruin him,
que lo pueden arruinar bueno no que lo
but that could ruin
pueden arruinar sino que pueda arruinar
their current relationship, come on  back don't
su actual relación ven hacia atrás no
look don't look
mires no mires
little girl Give me my life come
chiquita Dale mi vida ven
[Music]
[Música]
come He's laughing here at Aida Merlano
ven Se está riendo aquí de Aida merlano
imitating the situation or he's not
imitando la situación o no lo está
doing it
haciendo a
[Music]
[Música]
purpose
propósito
s wine thoroughbred
s vino pura
thoroughbred 100 million pesos
sangre pura sangre 100 millones de pesos
Wow I love it he
Wow Me encanta
calls for you and it's
llama para ti y se
called s for I have it marrito
llama s para lo tengo marrito muchas
thank you very much I love it I love it I have it
gracias Me encanta me encanta lo tengo
you G Oh I love it I
te G Oh me encanta me
love it I gave him what I gave him what eh I gave him what I
encanta yo le daba qué yo le daba qué eh
gave him much more than
yo le daba qué yo le daba mucho más que
you yes I give him writing to the boyfriend
tú sí yo le da escribiéndole al novio
many better things than you
muchas cosas mejores que tú
okay And by the way tell him to let me send
okay Y de paso dile que deje mandar
pictures no and he's better than me Ah and
fotos no y me la esta mejor que tú Ah y
and slowly he lets me send pictures at
y despacio que me deja mandar fotico en
night
las noches
[Music]
[Música]
like that believe Ah now now now Ah fish I
así cre Ah ahora ahora ahora Ah pesc yo
'm busy
esty ocupado
mom Oh no
mamá Ay no
[Music]
[Música]
and he has paid for this Cana see I don't I don't know
e es hab pagado esta Cana ve yo no yo no
anything about that type He barely gave you for a
s nada de ese tipo Apenas te dio por un
little horse of mine he wouldn't give you I gave him
caballito de mi no te daba yo le daba
many more things better than you by the way I
muchas más cosas mejores que tu de paso
told myself to send pictures and I sent him
que me dije de mandar foticos y le mandé
the face  and see see and you know I'll
la carita y vea vea y sabes que lo
show it at the end of the streaming if you
muestro al final del streaming si
want too
quieren también
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
to I put horns on the [ __ ] that I had
para le puse cachos a la [__] que tenía
like hca or so this What is I put
como hca o sea esto Qué es le puse los
horns on the [ __ ] that I had like wc
cachos a la [__] que tenía como wc
to What does this mean what does that mean
a Qué significa esto qué significa eso
a friend of wescol yesterday at a concert
un amigo de wescol ayer en un concierto
leaving Cook's in a song or so
dejando la de Cook en una canción o sea
a friend of wescol laughing at Aida
un amigo de wescol riéndose de Aida
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
merlano writing to your ex's partner
merlano escribirle a la pareja de tu ex
is not right not even in challenge because
no está bien ni siquiera en reto porque
one does not know how people deserve and
uno no sabe cómo merezcan las personas y
While you play to destabilize my
Mientras tú juegas a desestabilizar mi
relationship I can turn yours into [ __ ]
relación Yo te puedo volver [__] la
you imagine where that day I
tuya tú te imaginas donde ese dí yo
would have woken up crazy and I write to
hubiese amanecido loca y yo le escribo a
your girlfriend to bother her and suddenly I decide to
tu novia a molestarla y de repente a se
send her this little piece of chat
me da por mandarle este pedacito de chat
you remember this and I send him the
tú te acuerdas de esto y le mando el
complete context and I say Hey look it
contexto completo y le digo Oye mira
turns out that when he had just broken
resulta que cuando él acababa de
up with me and was trying
terminar conmigo y estaba intentando las
things with you he was talking to me about you
cosas contigo me estaba hablando de ti
but I would be incapable of doing those
pero yo sería incapaz de hacer esas
things so you don't have to do  what
cosas entonces no hay que hacer lo que
we don't like is that they do the same to us because of the
no nos gusta que nos hagan igual por la
way you [ __ ] in the DM
forma en la que te cagaste en el DM
when my husband wrote you, I think
cuando te escribió mi marido yo creo que
you realized that he doesn't find
te diste cuenta de que él tampoco le
those jokes very funny either, no,
hace mucha gracia a esos chistes que no
you didn't tell him that if it was time, it was time, you
tú no le dijiste que si tocaba tocaba tú
told him please, it's okay that you did
le dijiste que por favor la pas que tú
n't want problems with anyone.
no querías problemas con nadie Que
Forgive my immaturity and he forgave you, she
perdone la inmadurez y él te perdonó no
wasn't sentenced to jail because she's so
estaba condenada a cárcel por va tan
slow, she's in an appeal, but come on, that's it, I
lento está en un recurso pero vamos eso
think they're going to
yo creo que eso la van a volver a
sentence her again, I don't know if there, it's because I don't know
condenar yo no sé si allí es que no sé
what the law is like there. To what extent do you
cómo será allí la ley Hasta qué punto
know you can
sabes m puedes pagar cárcel con casa no
pay for jail with house arrest? It wasn't, it wasn't house arrest, but let's see, she actually committed the crime, I mean, she actually committed the crime, eh, it's quite likely that they'll sentence her again, you understand, in the appeal, I did
a condenar me entiendes en el recurso yo
n't because I came to the conclusion that
no porque yo llegué a la conclusión de
I didn't have the misfortune of giving birth to have to put
que yo no tuve la desgracia de parir
up with you and since you
como para tener que aguantarte y como tú
've come out and talked so much [ __ ] about me, I've
has salido a hablar tanta [__] de mí
remained silent, I decided to make
yo me he quedado callada decidí hacer
a reflection, the one that your community has been waiting for so long
una reflexión esa que tu comunidad tanto
because look every time
estaba esperando porque mira que siempre
you mention me They say jaida
que tú me mencionas Ellos dicen jaida
right now release a video jaida is preparing
ahorita saca video jaida está preparando
her reflection and I don't know where they get it from
su reflexión y no sé dónde se lo sacan
if I have never really answered you well In fact, I
si yo en realidad nunca te he respondido
think that maybe they live in
bien Es más creo que tal vez viven en
a reality as distorted as
una realidad tan distorsionada como la
yours but I'm going to remind you of a couple of
tuya pero yo te voy a recordar un par de
details that will make you
detalles que te van a hacer caer en
realize that the abuse of the mana
cuenta de que el abuso de la mana nos
atrophies our neurons because you're going to
atrofia las neuronas porque tú vas a
say Oh And I why didn't I remember
decir Ay Y yo por qué no me acordaba de
this I remember that you said Since I cut
esto yo me acuerdo que tú dijiste Desde
her out of my life I don't want to
que la saqué de mi vida yo no quiero
know anything more about that woman I'm at a
saber más nada de esa mujer estoy en un
point where talking about her
momento donde hablar de ella me me me
bothers me because I don't want to upset a a a the
fastidia porque no quiero incomodar a a
person I'm dating
a a la persona con la que estoy saliendo
right now dude she already has to
ahorita huevón ella ya tiene que
put up with a lot of things to
aguantar un montón de cosas como para
put up with a frustrated girlfriend but
aguantarse una novia frustrada pero
then you kept going and mentioning me
luego seguías y seguías mencionándome
this is current so I understood what it is that
esto es actual entonces entendí que es
wescol responding now they
que sea eso wescol respondiendo ahora no
are not constant taunts not from wescol now
son pullas constantes no de wescol ahora
no I mean wescol now let's see
no O sea wescol ahora vamos a ver la
wescol's response too  you
respuesta de wescol también hiciste
realized that you didn't cut me out of your
conciencia de que tú no me sacaste de tu
life I cut you out of mine That's why
vida yo te saqué de la mía Por eso eres
you're the one who's blocked I'm giving you some advice it's in
tú el bloqueado te doy un consejo es de
very bad taste to continue mentioning your ex when you're in a
muy mal gusto seguir mencionando a la ex
relationship because people
teniendo pareja porque las personas
could interpret it as if I'm
podrían interpretar como que soy
indelible insurmountable u but this phrase
imborrable insuperable u pero esta frase
is devastating for a lot of people no I mean
es demoledora para mucha gente no O sea
how many people are there who can't stop
cuánta gente hay que no deja de
mentioning their ex well look what's
mencionar a su expareja pues Mirad lo
saying there d merlano there no
que está diciendo ahí d merlano ahí no
Hey when Aida was fighting with
Oye que cuando Aida se peleaba con
Dallas there were a lot of people who supported her
Dallas había mucha gente que la apoyaba
no then they're going to use this phrase
no Entonces esta frase La van a usar
too unforgettable and you should
también inolvidable y tú deberías
protect your partner from those
blindar a tu pareja de esas
interpretations How strange isn't it that
interpretaciones Qué curioso no que
I have more consideration for your partner
tenga yo más consideración por tu pareja
than you well now let's start with what I
que tú bueno ahora sí empecemos con lo
want to tell you instead of
que te quiero decir en vez de estar
listening to a woman who doesn't even
escuchando una mujer que ni siquiera
practice what she says and you're going to realize
aplica lo que dice y te vas a dar cuenta
for all the times that I've ignored you
por todas las veces que te he ignorado
that my only mistake has been you of the
que mi único descache has sido tú del
rest I apply In fact I haven't had to
resto yo aplico De hecho no he tenido
say that I don't care I've
que decir que no me importa lo he
shown it I haven't had to say that I
demostrado no he tenido que decir que te
want to cut you out of my life I cut you out and the
quiero sacar de mi vida te saqué y la
reason why  I'm not answering you It's not
razón por la que no te respondo No es
because I don't have anything to do but because
porque no tenga con qué sino porque a mí
your existence is so repulsive to me
tu existencia me resulta tan repulsiva
that I was hoping that if I did
que yo guardaba la esperanza de que si
n't mention you one day you would get
no te mencionaba algún día tú te sacaras
my name out of your mouth Let's go to the most
mi nombre de tu boca Vámonos a lo más
recent, this is brief since you are
reciente que esto es breve como tú eres
such a child that you believe that everything is a
tan niño que tú crees que todo es un
game, I'm going to explain to you what for you
juego te voy a explicar lo que para ti
was a simple challenge was the excuse that
fue un simple reto fue la excusa que
your community found to find the
encontró tu comunidad para encontrar el
username of my sisters-in-law and
usuario de mis cuñadas y de la hija de
Juan's 13-year-old daughter to go bother them
Juan de 13 años para ir a molestarlos
So I have to call to say
Entonces yo tengo que llamar a decir
hi what happens is that before your
hola lo que pasa es que yo antes de tu
brother I was with a kid then
hermano estaba con un [__] entonces
Ignore the type of messages like this that
Ignora el tipo de mensajes como este que
are coming to you do you understand So
te están llegando lo entiendes Entonces
no, it's not a game, it's childish and
no no es un juego eso es una niñería y
curiously that was what
curiosamente eso fue lo que más te
offended you the most that I have said
ofendió a ti que yo he dicho
publicly that you were a child but in your
públicamente que eras un niño pero en tú
defense every time you mention me you
defensa cada que me mencionas te
behave like one Proving me right and your
comportas como tal Dándome la razón y tu
community studies during the day and in the
comunidad en el día estudia y en la
afternoon They are digital gang members now
tarde Son pandilleros digitales ahora
this happened after the challenge not even
esto pasó después del reto ni siquiera
after my partner's response  or
después de la respuesta de mi pareja ni
anything but let's go then in
nada pero vamos a irnos entonces en el
time to talk about what we haven't
tiempo para hablar de lo que no hemos
talked about it all starts when alofoke
hablado todo empieza cuando alofoke me
calls me to offer me the presidency of his
llama a ofrecerme la presidencia de su
team in the Queens League to whom he
equipo en la Queens League al fque que
was a colleague with whom I had a very
era un colega con quien tenía una muy
good relationship bro Look really bro I'm
buena relación bro Mira realmente bro te
going to tell you something I even think it's cool
voy a decir algo hasta me parece chimba
because as I say it's a show I didn't end with
pues como digo es show yo no terminé con
her on bad terms no it's nothing
ella en malos términos no no pasa nada
daddy it surprises me I mean they're
papi me extraña O sea que me están
using me they're using me Aida do you
utilizando me están utilizando Aida te
remember now don't you remember Now
acuerdas ahora no te acuerdas Ahora
when I defended that wcol wasn't a
cuando de defendía que wcol no era un
homophobe he wasn't sexist and he wasn't well well
homófobo no era machista y no era pues
a lot of things bro Look I'm
pues un montón de cosas bro Mira yo esty
used to people eating my
acostumbrado a que la gente coma
ribs every person who talks about
costillas mías toda persona que habla de
me or has a relationship with me That's how it's going to
mí o tiene relación conmigo Así va a
happen that's been going on for a long time I mean
pasar eso viene desde hace mucho o sea
I'm telling you it's something cool it's something good
yo te digo es algo chimba es algo bien a
people like the morbidity but
la gente le gusta el morbo pero también
I also take her into account She went because of her
yo la tomo en cuenta Ella fue por su
quality it wasn't because she was your girlfriend
cualidad no fue porque era novia tuya
bro Ah no no well that's fine
brother Ah no no pues eso está bien
excellent I believe you I'll explain it to you and she
excelente yo te creo yo te expli t ya no
's not a leftover of mine anymore But It's obvious that if
es una sobra mía Pero Es evidente que si
she wouldn't have been with me She wouldn't
ella no hubiera estado conmigo Ella no
be president Well here we're going
estuviera de presidenta Pues aquí vamos
to hide the truth my brother Oh they're
a tapar el sol con un dedo mi hermano Ay
going to know her internationally and in
la van a conocer internacionalmente y en
the kin league it's through westcoll nobody
la kin leag es por westcol a all nadie
knows her there Aida is an
la conoce allá Aida es una mujer
incredible woman she's going to break that and she's going to
increíble ella va a romper eso y lo va a
do excellent I'm telling you
hacer excelente yo te estoy diciendo el
why you set your sights on her and it's not
por qué tú te fijaste en ella y no está
bad suddenly Suddenly you liked her a
mal de de pronto De pronto te gustó un
little bit one doesn't know daddy why are we going to be
poquito uno no sabe papi para qué vamos
liars because obviously
a hacer mentirosos pues obviamente la
invite her because sea the tet I put it see We
invitar pues mar el tet yo lo puse vea
have a lot of people eating at
Tenemos un montón de gente comiendo a
our expense No matter how much you
costillas de nosotros No importa cuánto
read this it was always like this
leas esto siempre era así cosas de
pmpara things me since I'm not going to
pámpara yo ya que yo tampoco le voy a
throw Aida at her because she knows me
tirar Aida porque ella me conoce a mí
dude she she knows why ao because
huevón ella ella sabe por qué ao porque
she knows that I don't care she
ella sabe que a mí no me importa ella
preferred to win numbers and take advantage of
prefirió ganar números y aprovecharse de
that controversy with alofo those two
eso de polémica con alofo esos dos
numbers and well Yes that too that that
números y bueno Sí eso también eso eso
also happened but well br it's that I
también pasó pero pues br es que yo yo
what can I do dude life
qué puedo hacer huevón a mí la vida la
life has paid me badly life has
vida me ha pagado mal la vida me ha
paid me badly What am I going to make cry  I do
pagado mal Qué voy a hacer llorar ya yo
n't see a problem with that, dude. To
a eso no le ve un problema huevón real a
what I answer this in an
lo que yo respondo esto en una
interview, there is one thing that is completely
entrevista hay una cosa completamente
true. And it is that if I had not been
cierta Y es de no haber sido yo pareja
his partner, I would never have had the opportunity
de él nunca habría tenido la oportunidad
to enter a streaming scene.
de entrar a un escenario de streaming
That is a truth, an
eso es una verdad una verdad
absolutely unnecessary truth because one
absolutamente innecesaria porque una
thing is for you to make a statement and
cosa es que tú hagas una afirmación y
another thing is for you to go out and make those types
otra cosa es que salgas a hacer ese tipo
of statements about someone who at
de afirmaciones sobre alguien que en
some point was your wife. It was too much
algún momento fue tu mujer estuvo de más
for him to come out and say these things. Only
que él saliera a decir Estas cosas solo
this is something that one does not have to
que esto es algo que uno no le tiene que
explain to a man because a
explicar a un hombre porque un hombre de
real man knows it. So I assume my
verdad lo sabe entonces yo asumo mi
responsibility because I was the one who
responsabilidad porque fui yo quien se
messed with a child and that was the great
metió con un niño y esa fue la gran
offense that I made to you. I said that those
ofensa que te hice que dije que esas
things were not for men, that they were for
cosas no eran de hombre que eran de
children. The only thing I said was the
niños lo único que yo dije fue la
reality. For example, when I
realidad a mí por ejemplo cuando yo in
started with Aida, Aida got me
inicié con Aida e Aida me me consiguió
the advertisements and those things and
las las publicidades de y esas cosas y
Aida keeps 20% of those
Aida se queda un 20% de esas
advertisements because obviously that
publicidades porque evidentemente eso
was because of her and I did not have a problem
fue por ella y yo no no tenía problema
with that. I did not
con eso yo con eso Entonces en vez de
feel it as a threat or as if I
sentirlo como una amenaza o como que la
were for her.  of going down feel it like it is it is
estoy por de bajeando siéntelo como que
pampara and because it is pmpara it helped me I
es es pampara y por ser pámpara me ayudó
included her in the live shows with Germn I
la incluí en los directos con Germán le
introduced her to Kun I took her to the kins I
presenté al Kun la llevé a la kins le
introduced her to Piqu I introduced her to Arcngel I
presenté a Piqué le presenté a Arcángel
took her everywhere to
la llevaba con todos lados a que
meet people dudes that I didn't know already
conociera gente huevón que ya no conocía
And mind you That's not throwing anything in anyone's face I no I would
Y ojo Eso no es sacar nada en cara Yo no
never have talked about this if she
yo nunca hubiera hablado de esto si ella
wasn't saying that I was going
no estuviera diciendo que yo la estoy
down on her because that's false the
por de bajeando porque eso es falso lo
last thing I want is to have a relationship or
último que quiero es tener relación o
talk to a person that I've already cut out
hablar con una persona que ya yo saqué
of my life if you know what I mean I don't want to
de mi vida si me entiende Yo no quiero
know absolutely anything about that woman I do
saber absolutamente nada de esa mujer yo
n't want to know anything about that woman already live
no quiero saber nada de esa mujer ya ya
your life live your life Daddy already They
haga su vida siga su vida Papi ya Se
both got together to keep [ __ ]
juntaron los dos para seguir tirando
dude they're doing everything possible
huevón están haciendo todo lo posible
so that I respond and [ __ ] them it
para que yo le responda y les tire
turns out that I'm going to Mexico with my
resulta que me voy a México con mi
partner and my aunt to live an opportunity
pareja y mi tía a vivir una oportunidad
that was very nice for me and it turns out that
que era bien linda para mí y resulta que
while I'm living a moment
mientras yo estoy viviendo un momento
that for me is different that is
que para mí es diferente que es
super nice you were reacting in
superbonito estabas tú reaccionando en
streaming right now Aida is in
streaming en este momento Aida está en
Mexico because because  I have her working
México porque porque la tengo trabajando
there but she'll never get it out of her
allá pero nunca se le va a quitar de la
head she's already sitting down it's because of her
cabeza que ya está sentada es por su
boyfriend I'm feeding a lot of people
novio a a un montón de gente le estoy
and instead of taking and throwing away
dando de comer y en vez de [__] y tirar
the good ones they're out there I walk around the
la buena están por ahí ando por los
sides then I got her into streaming I
laditos entonces la metí en el streaming
got her into soccer and I got her into
la metí en el fútbol y la metí en la
music and after that she's ungrateful
música y tras de eso es desagradecida
at least go out and talk say something real let
mínimo salga y hable diga algo real
's talk So something real and this
hablemos Entonces algo real y esta
anecdote is really nice because it's also
anécdota es bien linda porque también es
the opportunity to get the thorn out of
la oportunidad de sacarme la espinita de
all the people who think that I was fixated
toda la gente que piensa que yo me fijé
on your money when you met me
en tu dinero cuando tú me conociste a mí
I had my penthouse my truck my
Yo tenía mi Penthouse mi camioneta mis
companies legally constituted
empresas legalmente constituida
basically I was already Aida when I
básicamente yo ya era Aida cuando yo te
met you You ate standing up at the
conocí a ti Tú comías parado en el Mesón
kitchen counter You didn't have a living room You didn't
de la cocina Tú no tenías sala Tú no
have a dining room and I remind you that I
tenías comedor y te recuerdo que yo te
explained to you How to monetize Instagram I
expliqué Cómo monetizar Instagram yo te
showed you how the guidelines worked and I got you
enseñé cómo funcionaban las pautas y te
a Guideline with a client of mine from
saqué una Pauta con un cliente mío de la
which I didn't commission anything that I recorded you I
que no comisione nada que yo te grabé te
edited you and even  I published Because while
edité y hasta te publiqué Porque estando
I was sitting on the floor while you
yo sentada en el piso mientras tú
were streaming I was
estabas en streaming estaba yo
publishing and then that money came in to
publicando y luego ese dinero entró para
pay for your first room your chairs so you would
pagar tu primera sala tus sillas para
n't eat standing up your washing machine
que no comieras de pie tu lavadora
so before you I lived like a
entonces antes de ti yo vivía como una
queen But how do I live burned girl
reina Pero cómo viv niña tamada ardida
versus burned slum XD Well let's
versus barrio bajero ardido XD bueno a
see but I do believe that it's true that if
ver pero yo sí creo que es verdad que si
he he or rather if it weren't for him she would
él él o sea que si no fuera por él ella
n't have mentioned him more yes it
no lo hubiera mencionar más a él sí que
's true that he is like
es verdad que él está como
constantly making mentions And
constantemente haciendo menciones Y
allusions to her not before me to a
alusiones a ella no antes de mí a a un
lot of people I am feeding that What you
montón de gente le estoy dando de comer
say sounds very ugly that is
eso Que dices se escucha muy feo eso es
as if I said you and your friends ate
como si yo dijera tú y tus amigos comían
my ribs just for the small
costillas mías solo por el pequeño
detail that the 7 million pesos
detalle de que los 7 millones de pesos
that if the market went monthly
que si iba el mercado mensualmente los
I put them why are you not going to make
ponía yo porque no le vas a hacer creer
people believe that I ate
a la gente que yo comía costillas
studio ribs when it's not true I paid for the market
estudas cuando no es cierto el mercado
for the house We had two
de la casa lo pagaba yo Teníamos dos
maids and I paid one of the
empleadas y yo pagaba una de las
maids we bought the
empleadas compramos los muebles
outdoor furniture and all the little things  and we
exteriores y todas las cositas y los
paid them half and half, so basically
pagamos mitad y mitad o sea básicamente
you weren't my husband you were my rumi and I
Tú no eras mi marido eras mi rumi Y yo
told them the first time look my
le dije a los la primera vez mira mi
audience isn't used to
audiencia no está acostumbrar el
streaming so there they're going to connect
streaming Así que ahí se va a conectar
like 100 200 people had only
como 100 200 personas tuvieron solo
3,000 viewers yeah a minute of silence
3,000 viewers sí Un minuto de silencio
for that and I finished that stream happy
por eso y yo terminé ese Stream feliz
thinking that there were 2000 what happens is that
pensando que eran 2000 lo que pasa es
unlike you I'm happy with
que a diferencia de ti yo esty feliz con
little you on the contrary having it
poquito tú por el contrario teniéndolo
all you feel empty maybe because you haven't
todo te sientes vacío quizás porque no
understood that beyond your fame and
has entendido que más allá de tu fama y
your numbers what really gives you
tus números lo que realmente te da
values is who you are as a human being and that's
valores quién eres como ser humano y ahí
where one wonders what would become of you
es donde uno se pregunta Qué sería de ti
without flat I humbly had 995,000
sin flat yo tuve humildemente 995,000
people watching my game Oh I can't
personas viendo mi partido Ay no puedo
believe it but I lost Galacticas del Caribe
creer per perdió Galácticas del Caribe
that woman is losing everywhere
esa mujer está perdiendo en todos lados
dude my God my God you saw that you're
huevón Dios mío Dios mío viste que eres
a child a real man doesn't compete
un niño un hombre de verdad no compite
with his ex and then goes and says that they have to
con la ex y después coge y dice que
mention her so that
tienen que mencionar a ella para poder
the song can get a rating someone
que la canción tenga rating alguien que
explain to her why the song
le explique a ella por qué la canción
has a rating your friends  they make a
tiene rating tus amigos hacen una
song in which they put my voice and they
canción en la que meten mi voz y me
mention me to which I obviously
mencionan a lo que evidentemente yo
come out to respond But you are so
salgo a responder Pero tú eres tan
self-centered that like everything It's always about
egocéntrico que como todo Siempre se
you To you that seemed absurd
trata de ti a ti eso te pareció absurdo
So yes I mentioned your friend it's
Entonces sí yo mencioné a tu amigo es
true I mentioned it after he did a
cierto lo mencioné después de que hiz un
Live with you hanging off our
Live contigo colgándose de nuestra
breakup insinuating things to make me feel
ruptura insinuando cosas para dejarme
bad and also treating me badly then
mal y aparte tratándome de mal entonces
I respond that he is not an example of anything
yo respondo que él no es ejemplo de nada
because it seemed to me that he had no criteria
porque me parecía que no tenía criterio
to give an opinion on our relationship and
para opinar de nuestra relación y
curiously look how time proves me
curiosamente mira que el tiempo me da la
right because today he is in everyone's mouth
razón porque hoy está en Boca de todo el
for being promiscuous and for being a horny I put
mundo por promiscuo y por cachón puse
cach since I had like hu schools I
cach ya que tenía como hu escolas
would have preferred to find out from
hubiese preferido enterarme por boca de
my ex's mouth than from him but the truth is I am
mi ex que por él pero la verdad Se le
very grateful and she knows that I never
agradece mucho y ella sabe que nunca le
put Cacho Yes you understand me he wants to
puse Cacho Sí me entiendes me quiere
throw all those ladies those old ladies on me
tirar todas esas señoras esas viejitas
daddy your other friend in an attempt
papi encima tu otro amigo en un intento
to ridicule me says I put [ __ ] on
por ridiculizarme dice le puse cachos a
a [ __ ] like you put them on me
una [__] como tú me los pusiste a mí
this came out of his mouth not from your
esto salió de la boca de él no de la
mouth  mine I obviously react but
boca mía yo evidentemente reacciono pero
you find it outrageous that I come out and
a ti te parece indignante que yo salga a
say that because according to you I know that you
decir eso porque según tú yo sé que tú
never cheated on me So
nunca me pegaste los cachos Entonces por
why do you allow your friend to say that is that
qué tú permites que tu amigo lo diga es
maybe it is easier for you to complain
que acaso te queda más fácil reclamarle
to a woman than to complain to a man do you
a una mujer que reclamarle a un hombre
not have the capacity to stand in the line Although it's
no das para pararte en la raya Aunque
a lie I already realized because how you
mentira Ya me di cuenta porque como te
screwed me no then I understood Why do
le cagaste a m no entonces entendí Por
you fight with women apart she says No
qué te peleas con mujeres aparte dice No
She knows that I didn't cheat on her
Ella sabe que yo no le puse los cuernos
how does she know I mean if she doesn't know she
como lo sabe O sea si no lo sabe ella
knows what she knows what she doesn't know No
sabe lo que ella sabe lo que no sabe No
she knows how far she knows I admit it
ella sabe hasta dónde sabe Admito
publicly It's strange that a friend sings
públicamente Es raro que un amigo cante
that in a song Not just because of his face not without
eso en una canción No por la cara no sin
his permission I mean a friend does that to you
permiso de él o sea un amigo te hace eso
puts out a song on stage and says
saca una canción en un escenario y larga
something that he knows no and that turns you on I mean it does
una cosa que sabe no y que te pone o sea
n't make sense that it is without permission it
no tiene sentido que sea sin permiso no
is not a reason to get angry with your
es un motivo como para enfadarte con tu
friend no I was the one who said that I was the one who
amigo no yo fui el que dice eso yo fui
said that evil I admit it already I
el que dice esa maldad lo Admito ya ya
had to admit it and I'm
ya lo tenía que admitir y lo estoy
saying it you had to have an opinion  of my
diciendo tenías que opinar de mi
relationship twice for you to tell me it has to
relación dos veces para que a mí me dec
be something that I say is
los tiene que ser algo que yo diga es
better than me and I've never seen that.
mejor que yo y eso yo nunca lo he visto
Oh, a lot of kept women, there are so many kept women
hón mucha mantenida hay tanta mantenida
with so many empowered women, [ __ ] that they
con tanta mujer empoderada huevón que
even need a
hasta necesitan de necesitan de un
speech to feel better. If you are so
discurso para sentirse mejor Si tan
empowered, [ __ ], why aren't
empoderadas son huevón por qué no son
you the ones giving away the horse? Oh,
ustedes las que regalan el caballo Ay
but what are you complaining about if I gave you
pero de qué te quejas si yo te di
expensive gifts. In fact, I took you to Cancun, you did
regalos caros de hecho te llevé a Cancún
n't pay anything. I took you to Finland,
no pagaste nada te llevé por Finlandia
Italy, Spain, first class,
Italia España en primera la clase de
birthday party. And what happened when my
cumpleaños y qué pasó cuando llegó mi
birthday came? You told me, my love, I'm not
cumpleaños que me dijiste mi amor no te
going to give you anything expensive because I don't want
voy a regalar nada caro porque no quiero
you to become a materialistic woman.
que te vuelvas una mujer Materialista
Then clarify to people that I'm
entonces aclara a la gente que yo
not materialistic, but of course they can't
Materialista no soy pero claro es que no
reach the level of a man by
pueden llegar al nivel del hombre
having that attitude of a woman. The
teniendo esa actitud de mujer igual lo
good thing is that when you
bueno es que lo bueno es que ha al
give a horse, it already has time for him to
regalar un caballo ya tiene para que lo
put it in the room. Don't lie, don't go
meta en la sala no menti no hayan a
out, empowered girls, calm down. Okay, they're
salir chicas empoderadas tranquilas Okay
going to pay you the rent. Do you think
ya les van a pagar el arrienda Tú crees
that people didn't want me to give my opinion
que la gente no quería que yo opinara
about your two girlfriends?  in record time
Sobre tus dos novias en tiempo récord
after we broke up and you and I
después de que terminamos y tú y yo
know that if I had wanted
sabemos que si hubiese querido números
interaction numbers I would have just posted a
de interacción nada más publicaba una
screenshot and that was it because I knew the
captura y listo porque yo sabía el
full context of all your
contexto completo de todas tus
relationships along with what you
relaciones junto con lo que me
confessed to me a 400 million watch
confesaste un un relo de 400 millones sí
was a role that he had one He kept it let's
era un roles que tenía una Se lo quedó í
see if he gives it back to me how strong one sees
ver si me lo devuelve qué fuerte uno ve
is and says oh the man spent 400
es y dice ay el man se gastó 400
million on a watch doesn't it turns out he
millones en un reloj no resulta que él
was closing a deal with a man he
estaba cerrando un negocio con un señor
saw a watch and said oh daddy chn it's
le vio un reloj y le dijo uy pap chín va
a watch and the man said oh yeah spend
de reloj y el señor le dijo uy si pase
10 million and I'll give it to him he gave him the 10
10 millones y se lo doy le dio los 10
million the man gave him the watch and Lu he
millones el seor le dio el reloj y Lu él
gave me the watch but if you
me regaló a mí el reloj pero si estás
need it I'll send it to you so you
necesitando yo te lo mando para que lo
can pawn it so you can sell it I don't know because you
empeñes para que lo vendas no sé pues me
left me worried when you told me the
dejaste preocupada cuando me dijiste la
last time when How much is 10
última vez cuando Cuántos son 10
million How much is 10 million Omar told me
millones Cuántos son 10 millones me dijo
that you gave him a deadline to pay you
Omar que le diste un plazo para pagarte
Thanks we are here with some
Gracias estamos acá con con unos gastos
super low expenses for  everything about the launch and
super lgos por todo lo del lanzamiento y
you know that all the hotels and all the
sabes que todos los hoteles y todos los
flights for like 20 people I'll pay for them
vuelos como de 20 personas los pago yo
So we're we're not
Entonces estamos estamos agillo no está
agillo of money the toilet eh 00 euros dollars
agillo de dinero el wc eh 00 eur dólares
dollars 2,500 or rather the guy said in
dólares 2,500 o sea el tipo ha dicho en
that clip bragging about money that
ese clip vacilando de dinero que le
the watch cost him $1,000 00,000 and that he
costó el reloj $1,000 00,000 y que se lo
kept it for Aida but it turns out that it's
quedó a Aida pero es que resulta que son
2,500 what it really cost him when you
2,500 lo que le costó en verdad cuando
owed me money that you needed a deadline
me debías plata que necesitabas un plazo
Because at that time you didn't have the money
Porque en ese momento no tenías dinero
to pay me which surprised me
para pagarme cosa que me sorprendió
because you're such a millionaire I gave you
porque tú eres tan millonario yo le deo
ID 50 million it's that you're a big mouth
ID 50 millones es que tú eres muy bocón
And that's a problem I'm going to give you a
Y eso es un problema Te voy a poner un
personal example that Cyber truck
ejemplo personal esa Cyber truck con la
that you took pictures with in your garage is mine
que te hiciste fotos en tu garaje es mía
and I don't go around bragging
y yo no ando por ahí fanfarroneando
now This is not all because when I
ahora Esto no es todo porque cuando le
asked my team you took pictures in your
pedí a mi equipo hiciste fotos en tu
garage it's mine And that's a problem I'm
garaje es mía Y eso es un problema Te
going to give you a personal example that
voy a poner un ejemplo personal esa
Cyber truck with the Cyber truck that you
Cyber truck con el Cyber truck la que te
took pictures in your  garage is mine and I do
hiciste fotos en tu garaje es mía y yo
n't go around bragging now
no ando por ahí fanfarroneando ahora
This isn't all because when I asked
Esto no es todo porque cuando le pedí a
my team to make a compilation of
mi equipo que hiciera una compilación de
all the times that he had spoken badly
todas las veces que le había hablado mal
about me it added up to 35 minutes in summary
de mí sumaban 35 minutos resumidos
So this is like 5% because if not
Entonces esto es como el 5% porque si no
neither parents nor children last that long in another
ni padres e hijos dura tanto en otra
life You will not be my most humble moment
vida Tú no seras mi momento más humilde
But since we only have this one please
Pero como solo tenemos esta por favor Ya
Stop reminding me I'm going to give you some
deja de recordármelo te voy a dar un
advice Take my name out of your mouth and
consejo Sácate mi nombre de la boca y
respect my family If the day that I
respeta mi familia si el día que yo
get pregnant you give me
llegue a estar embarazada tú me haces
a bad time and you end up
pasar siquiera un mal rato y llegas a
putting the life of one of my children at risk
poner en riesgo la vida de un hijo mío
because of your nonsense I swear on everything that is
por tus babosadas yo te juro por todo lo
most sacred that I will make you regret it
más sagrado que voy a hacer que te pese
every day of your life There you will
todos los días de tu vida Ahí vas a
understand the difference between a person
entender la diferencia entre una persona
who claims to have power and one that really
que dice tener poder y una que realmente
has it May God bless you and make you
lo tiene que Dios te bendiga y te haga
see reason
entrar en razón
buah here papean eh here
buah aquí papean eh aquí
[Music]
[Música]
papean foreign
papean foreign